http://www.cbc.dk/privacy-policy/

GDPR Privacy Policy
At Cross-Border Communications we respect your right to data privacy. This is why any personal data we process is done with strict confidentiality and with the highest degree of care and security.
Here’s what you need to know:
Cross-Border Communications is a private limited company based at Ryesgade 3B, 2200 Copenhagen, Denmark. Our company registration number (CVR) is 26172462.
Your data is collected in the following situations:On our website (including through cookies)When you contact usWhen you apply for a jobIf you have sent us an email
We process your data based on a legitimate interest when you visit our website. This includes:Your IP addressInformation about your browser, including plug-insYour behaviour on our websiteCookiesContact email information, if provided
We use third party software-providers, who process your data on our behalf. Some of our providers are established in the US and have committed to comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.
We use cookies to track what part of our website you visit. In the table below, you can see which cookies we use and what they do. The data is transferred to our 3rd party suppliers of media advertising, statistical behaviour of users and tracking.
Name
Provider
Purpose
Duration
Type
CookieConsent
cbc.dk
Stores the users cookie consent for this website.
1 year
HTTP
Google Tag Manager
cbc.dk
Used by Google Tag Manager to load tracking scripts.
1 year
HTTP
Google Analytics
cbc.dk
Used to collect and send data of the visitor to Google Analytics.
1 year
HTTP
Lead Forensics
cbc.dk
Used to collect and send data of potential lead to Lead Forensics from contact formular.
1 year
HTTP
LinkedIn
Cookie
Used by LinkedIn to track if the visitor is using embedded services.
1 year
HTTP
hs_ab_test
www.cbc.dk
This cookie is used by the website’s operator in context with multi-variate testing. This is a tool used to combine or change content on the website. This allows the website to find the best variation/edition of the site.
Session
HTTP
vuid
Vimeo
Collects data on the user's visits to the website, such as which pages have been read.
2 years
HTTP
rc::a
Google
This cookie is used to distinguish between humans and bots. This is beneficial for the website, in order to make valid reports on the use of their website.
Persistent
HTML
rc::b
Google
This cookie is used to distinguish between humans and bots.
Session
HTML
rc::c
Google
This cookie is used to distinguish between humans and bots.
Session
HTML
local_storage_support_test
Twitter
The cookie is used in context with the local-storage function in the browser. This function allows the website to load faster by pre-loading certain procedures.
Persistent
HTML
__cfduid
www.cbc.dk
Used by the content network, Cloudflare, to identify trusted web traffic.
29 days
HTTP
__cfruid [x2]
www.cbc.dk
This cookie is a part of the services provided by Cloudflare - Including load-balancing, deliverance of website content and serving DNS connection for website operators.
Session
HTTP
Hubspot
lfuuid
Leadforensics
Tracks the individual sessions on the website, allowing the website to compile statistical data from multiple visits. This data can also be used to create leads for marketing purposes.
3376 days
HTTP
IDE
Google
Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.
1 year
HTTP
test_cookie
Google
Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies.
1 day
HTTP
common/cavalry_endpoint.php
Facebook
Collects data on visitor behaviour from multiple websites, in order to present more relevant advertisement - This also allows the website to limit the number of times that they are shown the same advertisement.
Session
Pixel
NID
Google
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
6 months
HTTP
yt-remote-fast-check-period
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML
yt-remote-session-app
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML
pagead/1p-user-list/#
Google
Tracks if the user has shown interest in specific products or events across multiple websites and detects how the user navigates between sites. This is used for measurement of advertisement efforts and facilitates payment of referral-fees between websites.
Session
Pixel
__ptq.gif
Hubspot
Sends data to the marketing platform Hubspot about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.
Session
Pixel
embed/v3/counters.gif
Hubspot
Collects information on user preferences and/or interaction with web-campaign content - This is used on CRM-campaign-platform used by website owners for promoting events or products.
Session
Pixel
__widgetsettings
Twitter
This cookie is set by Twitter - The cookie allows the visitor to share content from the website onto their Twitter profile.
Persistent
HTML
i/jot
Twitter Inc.
Sets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisement. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which facilitates real-time bidding for advertisers.
Session
Pixel
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
YouTube
Tries to estimate the users' bandwidth on pages with integrated YouTube videos.
179 days
HTTP
YSC
YouTube
Registers a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
Session
HTTP
yt-remote-cast-installed
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML
yt-remote-connected-devices
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Persistent
HTML
yt-remote-device-id
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Persistent
HTML
yt-remote-session-name
YouTube
Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video
Session
HTML
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across multiple websites. The purpose of this is to expose the visitor to relevant advertising, when visiting other websites.
We also process personal data when you consent to receive our newsletter, namely:NameEmailPhone number
This data will be stored for as long as you have signed-up for the newsletter or until we stop sending newsletters. Furthermore, we will use your email to build generic profiles and monitor on a personal and statistical level the open and click-through-rate of our newsletters. You can recall your consent through the link found at the bottom of each newsletter or by contacting us directly.
We will store your data in our CRM system based on legitimate interest in you as a potential customer. This includes:NamePositionCompany nameCompany addressEmail address (if provided)Linked-In profile
Your data will be transferred to our CRM system provider marketing automation system provider.
You can always contact us rk@cbc.dk or +45 35 25 01 60 if you need clarification about:What personal data we processData you would like rectifiedData you would like erasedLimiting our processing of your dataWithdrawing consent
Thank you.
Let's make things happen.
© Cross-Border Communications | All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy | Cookie settings
